ISAAC ONGECHI MOBE

Address | P.O.BOX 00511 | Ongata-Rongai | 0719359223 | isaacmongechi@gmail.com

PROFILE

Highly motivated IT consultant with extensive customer service and business experience. Possess a strong knowledge of computer fundamentals and Keep abreast of new software applications. Incorporate the newest computer technologies together with programming languages to deliver high quality work efficiently and indipendently. Equipped with an indepth understanding of team work and remote work from working with high level officials and community members.

WORK EXPERIENCE

I.E.B.C | OPP. NTSA, LIKONI RD, NAIROBI

CASUAL EMPLOYEE

JUNE 2022 TO JULY 2022

Served as a casual employee during the preparations for 2022 general elections, packaging and preparation of the equipment used during elections. Developed a great understanding of warehouse stock management and team work skills during the period.

OKETCH FOODSTUFFS | OPP. LAVINGTON MALL

SENIOR SALES ASSOCIATE

JULY 2017 TO PRESENT

Delivered food for a small food business for two months as a part Time job. Developed business communication skills during the period to increase customer activity for the business.

EDUCATION

HIGHSCHOOL

JANUARY 2016 TO 2019

Studied for a high school certificate of a C- grade at Nakeel boys highschool located at Gataka road.

CERTIFICATE/DIPLOMA

SEPTEMBER 2020 TO PRESENT

Enrolled for a Diploma in Business Information Technology in 2021 at Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology expected to graduate in the current year.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office. Frontend Development/design.

Jetbrains IDES. Research skills and Project management.

Adobe Creative Suite. Business Communication.

PROJECTS

Worked on an online doctor appointment booking system for my final year project as a training opportunity for the field and to get a better understanding of the various technologies used in computer systems. I have worked on various personal portfolio websites to orient myself with different technologies like HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT and programming languages like PHP and PYTHON. Please visit my github to see some of my practical projects. https://github.com/isaacmobe